Register of the Elizabeth Churchill Brown Papers 1943-1984
Hoover Institution Archives
- SUBJECT FILES, 1837-1984
  - Javits, Jacob. Biographical sketch, newsletters, pamphlets, press releases, reprints, transcripts, 1965-1976 (Folder 12)
    - General, 1966-1976
    - Speeches and writings, 1965-1966
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. Clippings, correspondence, notes, press releases, transcripts, 1953-1966 (Folder 13)
    - General, 1961-1966
    - Correspondence with Lyndon Johnson and others, 1959-1964
    - Speeches and writings. Includes typescript copy of a newspaper column written by L.B. Johnson, substituting for Constantine Brown, 1953
  - Kennedy, Edward. Correspondence, flyers, newsletters, 1969-1973 (Folder 14)
    - General, 1969-1973
    - Correspondence, 1969
  - Kennedy, John. Correspondence, newsletters, notes, press releases, 1953-1978 (Folder 15)
    - General, 1961-1978
    - Correspondence with John F. Kennedy and others, 1953-1961
    - Speeches and writings. Mimeographed transcripts, 1961-1962
  - Kennedy, Robert. Correspondence, miscellany, newsletters, 1962-1970 (Folder 16)
    - General. Newsletters, miscellany, and correspondence with William Loeb, 1962-1970
    - Speeches and writings. Mimeographed transcripts, 1962
  - Kissinger, Henry. Newsletters, 1969-1975 (Folder 17)
  - Knight, Frances. Correspondence, memoranda, newsletters, notes, press releases, transcripts, SEE ALSO: CORRESPONDENCE/Knight, Frances, 1954-1973. (Folder 18)
    - General, 1954-1973
    - Correspondence with John Phillips, c. 1955
  - Korea
    - General. Includes anonymous typescript report, The Korean Confusion, correspondence with Newsweek, and others, 1958 (Folder 19)
    - Foreign relations. Newsletters, pamphlets, press releases, reports, wire reports, 1947-1976
      - Japan. Includes statements by Yiu Tai Ha (Chief, Republic of Korea Mission in Japan), 1958-1959 (Folder 20)
      - United States. Includes printed report by the Korean Foreign Policy Association, Comments on the Korea Section of the Conlon Report, 1947-1976
    - Internal affairs. Newsletters, pamphlets, serial issues, printed copy (pamphlet) of Hong Chong-in, The March of Korean Journalism: A Birds Eye View, the Korean Foreign Policy Association, Korea's Internal Political Situation, and printed pamphlets relating to the National Security Law, SEE ALSO: CORRESPONDENCE/Rhee, Syngman, 1953-1971. (Folder 21)
    - Korean War, 1950-1953 (Box 30)
      - General. Prisoners of war (Folder 1)
        - General. Memoranda, newsletters, pamphlets, reports, mimeographed statements relating to incidents in United Nations P.O.W. camps, wire reports, 1952-1959
        - Correspondence, 1956-1958
      - Correspondence with Summers, Paul D., Jr., SEE ALSO: CORRESPONDENCE/Clarke, General Carter, 1952. (Folder 2)
      - Non-printed material, 1950-1953
        - General. Correspondence, flyers, reports, transcripts, wire reports, and a typescript report, Intelligence Estimate of the Situation in Korea, 1950-c. 1952 (Folder 3)
        - Reports, 1950-c. 1952 (Folder 3-4)
          - Ingram, Sam, The Puzzle of American Policy, Mimeographed copy, c. 1952.
          - Wiley, Alexander, Smith, H. Alexander, Hickenlooper, Bourke B., and Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr., Background to Korea. Mimeographed report, 1950
        - Statements by Omar Bradley, Harry F. Byrd, Claire L. Chennault, Robert C. Hendrickson, Douglas MacArthur. Mimeographed copies, 1950-1953 (Folder 5)
      - Printed material. Clippings, newsletters, pamphlets, 1950-1971 (Folder 6)
    - Maps, 1945-c. 1953 (Folder 7)
  - Latin America
    - General (Folder 8)
      - General. Clippings, lists, newsletters, pamphlets, 1958-1976
      - Correspondence with Thomas J. Dodd, 1963
    - Communist influence. Lists, notes, newsletters, pamphlets, press releases, serial issue (Carib), and mimeographed report, Statistical Data on Communist Propaganda Activities in Latin America-1958, 1958-1981 (Folder 9)
  - Middle East. Clippings, notes, press releases, serial issues, mimeographed transcripts of speeches of Jamil baroody (Saudi Arabian Ambassador) at the United Nations, and correspondence with Mahmoud About Fath and Irving Zuckerman, 1948-1974. (Folder 10-11)
  - Miscellany, 1837-1976
    - General. Biographical sketches, clipping, newsletters, notes, phonograph record, pamphlet, printed article, 1969-1975 (Folder 12)
    - Books and authors, 1952-1976 (Folder 13)
      - General. Bibliographies, clippings, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, promotional material, 1953-1976
      - Correspondence with Paul Dever, the Devin-Adair Co., Publishers, 1952
    - Quotations, Notes and photocopy of Joseph Hopkinson, Memoirs of John Marshall, 1837-1974. 1837 (Folder 14)
  - Nixon, Richard M.
    - General. Clippings, correspondence, memoranda, newsletters, notes, 1952-1969
      - General (Folder 15)
      - Reports (White House), Mimeographed copies, 1971-1972. (Folder 16)
      - Speeches and writings. Mimeographed transcripts, including correspondence, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Watergate. Correspondence, newsletters, 1973-1976 (Folder 2)
  - Pakistan. Pamphlets, press release, and printed copies (pamphlets) of Malik Firoz Khan Noon, Democratic Ideals and Foreign Policy of Pakistan, the Ministry of Law, The Basic Democracies Order, and the Department of Advertising, Films and Publications, Introduction to Basic Democracies in Pakistan, 1958-1959 (Folder 3)
  - Panama (Folder 4)
    - General. Clippings, form letters, press releases, reports, 1960-1977
    - Correspondence with Daniel J. Flood, 1959-1966
  - Poland. Clippings, notes, reports, serial issues, printed transcripts, 1945-1969 (Folder 5)
  - Portugal (Angola). Newsletters and notes, 1974-1976 (Folder 6)
  - Reagan, Ronald. Form letter, promotional material, transcript excerpts, c. 1975-1977 (Folder 7)
  - Rhodesia. Flyers, form letter, newsletters, notes, 1966-1978 (Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. Biographical sketch, copies of articles, newsletters, 1951-1974 (Folder 9)
  - Rostow, Walt Whitman. Biographical sketch, clippings, notes, pamphlets, transcripts, and photocopy of portions of a typescript report (by Rostow?), 1962-1967 (Folder 10)
  - Rusk, Dean (Folder 11)
    - General. Newsletter, notes, quotations, transcripts, 1950-1964
    - Speeches and writings. Pamphlets, 1951-1964
  - Schlesinger, Arthur, Jr. (Folder 12)
    - General. Excerpts from printed article, newsletters, notes, 1946-1962
    - Correspondence with the Washington Evening Star regarding a column by Constantine Brown, 1961
  - South Africa (Folder 13)
    - General. Flyers, newsletters, pamphlets, transcripts, and a printed report by W.C. Naude, South Africa: A Western Society, 1961-c. 1981
    - Correspondence. W.C. Naude (South African Ambassador to U.S.), including speech transcript, South Africa Today, 1961
  - Spain. Charts, clippings, correspondence, maps, newsletters, pamphlets, reports, statements by the Rev. Jose Mateo, M.D. Forrest, and Fidel Sanz, c. 1949-1975 (Folder 14)
  - Stevenson, Adlai (Folder 15)
    - General. Clippings, flyer, form letter, newsletters, notes, 1952-1964
    - Correspondence with Clarence J. Brown, Fred E. Busbey, Carl T. Curtis, George A. Dondero, William E. Jenner, James P. Kem, Alfred Kohlberg, Joseph W. Martin, Jr., Chapman Revercomb, Andrew F. Schoeppel, and others, 1952
  - Tibet. Printed copies of American-Asian Educational Exchange, Inc., Genocide in Tibet: A Study in Communist Aggression (pamphlet), and Lowell Thomas, The Rape of Tibet (reprint), 1959-1967 (Folder 16)
  - Truman, Harry S. Form letter and notes, c. 1952 (Folder 17)
  - Turkey. Biographical sketches, map, newsletters (includes issue of Newsletter on Contemporary Communism by Ruth Fischer, notes, press releases, reports, correspondence with Max W. Bishop, 1946), 1946-1959 (Folder 18)
  - U.S.S.R.
    - General (Folder 19)
      - General. Newsletters, pamphlets, reports, 1954-1971
      - Correspondence. John J. McCloy to George A. Dondero, 1944
    - Economic policy. Printed copy of A. Leontyev, Toward a Classless Society: The Second Five-Year Plan Explained, 1932 (Folder 20)
    - Foreign relations
      - General. Clippings, newsletters, pamphlets, press releases, reprints, transcripts, printed copy (pamphlet) of G. Dimitroff, The United Front Against Fascism and War, interview transcripts of V.M. Molotov with W.R. Hearst and J. Kingsbury Smith, and of N. Khrushchev with the Foreign Broadcast Information Service, a photocopy of a printed article, V.M. Molotov, The International Situation and the Foreign Policy of the Soviet Government, and a printed copy of Statement of the Moscow Conference of Representatives of Communist and Workers Parties, 1935-1974 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
      - Eastern Europe. Notes and reprints, 1940-1978 (Folder 3)
      - United States
        - General. Correspondence, newsletters, pamphlets, reports, mis statements by Anastas I. Mikoyan, 1957-1974 (Folder 4)
        - Diplomatic relations. Clippings and mimeographed transcript of testimony by A.C. Wedemeyer, 1954 (Folder 5)
        - Khrushchev visit. Correspondence, flyers, form letters, memoranda, newsletters, notes, press releases, speech excerpts, reports, 1959
          - General (Folder 6)
          - Anti-Khrushchev material (Folder 7)
        - Summit conferences. Correspondents, notes, pamphlets, printed reports, mimeographed copy of speech by Barry Goldwater, c. 1954-1960 (Folder 8)
        - Treaties. Newsletters and reports, SEE ALSO: Defense/Treaties, 1948-1969 (Folder 9)
    - Government. Biographical sketches, newsletters, notes, pamphlets and a printed copy of the constitution of the U.S.S.R., 1939-1969 (Folder 10)
    - History. Excerpts, 1854 and 1935 (Folder 11)
      - Kelly, Walter K., The History of Russia, 1854
      - Knorin, W., Communist Party of the Soviet Union: A Short History, 1935.
    - Internal affairs
      - General. Newsletters, pamphlets, press release, poem, reports, interview transcript, printed copies of D.Z. Manuilsky, The Results of Socialist Reconstruction in the U.S.S.R., and of a speech by L.I. Brezhnev The 50th Anniversary of the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1935-1972 (Folder 12-13)
      - Dissent and repression. Newsletters, press releases, printed pamphlets, 1959-1983 (Folder 14)
    - Military affairs. Correspondence, flyer, printed article and newsletters, 1957-c. 1977 (Folder 15)
  - United States - Domestic issues and programs
    - General (Folder 16)
      - Amnesty. Newsletter, 1972
      - Consumer protection. Newsletter and flyer, 1971-c. 1975
      - Energy. Mimeographed copy of Robert Bleiberg, Oil Shortage--American Style, c. 1973
      - Ethnic minorities, Italian-American. Press release, 1970
      - Gun control. Newsletters, 1966-1975
    - New Deal. Biographical sketches, newsletter, printed speech transcripts. Includes typescript reports prepared for Karl Mundt regarding Harry L. Hopkins and David K. Niles, 1940-1959 (Folder 17)
    - Poverty and welfare programs. Flyers and newsletters, 1965-1975 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Press and media issues
      - General, 1950-1983 (Folder 2)
        - General. Clippings, memoranda, newsletters, notes, serial issue (Carib), 1950-1983
        - Expose. Periodical issues, 1951 Nov. 1-1953 Jan. (Folder 3-4)
      - Correspondence (not for publication) with the American Legion Magazine, the Harvard Fortnightly, Modern Age, the Washington Times Herald, and others, 1952-1972 (Folder 5)
    - Unemployment. Newsletter and transcripts of speeches by Homer Ferguson, c. 1952-1959 (Folder 6)
    - Urban renewal and development. Excerpts from articles, newsletters, and printed copy (pamphlet) issued by the New Times, The Slums of New York, 1957-1977 (Folder 7)
    - Womens movement/ERA. Biographical sketches, newsletters, resolutions, and correspondence with Carl T. Curtis, 1950-1974 (Folder 8)
  - United States - Foreign relations
    - General. Copies of articles, newsletters, notes, press releases, reports, mimeographed copy of conference report of the American Political Science Association, Research on American Foreign Policy, transcripts of speeches by Viscount Montgomery (typescript), Herbert Hoover, The Protection of Freedom, (reprint) and Mike Mansfield, Foreign Policy and the Democratic Majority, (mimeograph), 1956-1980. (Folder 9)
    - Economic policy
      - General. Correspondence, press releases, reports, Includes mimeographed copy of report of the Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Inc., Foreign Economic Policy for the Twentieth Century, and excerpts from a mimeographed report by Allen J. Ellender, Correspondence, press releases, reports, Includes mimeographed copy of report of the Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Inc., Foreign Economic Policy for the Twentieth Century, and excerpts from a mimeographed report by Allen J. Ellender, 1955-1961. 1955; 1957 1955-1961. 1955; 1957 (Folder 10-12)
      - Foreign aid
        - General
          - Non-printed material, Biographical sketches, charts, form letters, press releases, statements by Styles Bridges, John Marshall Butler, Thomas J. Dodd, William E. Jenner, Otto E. Passman, and Lawrence H. Smith, Includes typescript copies of Arthur G. Trudeau, Some Comments Regarding our American Foreign Policy, and Where Are We?, and a mimeographed copy of the report of the Commission on Organization of the Executive Branch of the Government, Overseas Economic Operations, 1952-1974. 1952-1974. 1955 (Box 34, Folder 1-4)
          - Printed material, Clippings, newsletters, pamphlets, reports, reprints, transcripts. Includes printed copies of U.S. Dept. of Commerce, Foreign Aid by the United States Government, 1940-1952, and Foreign Aid by the United States Government, printed copies of U.S. Dept. of State, Point Four Pioneers, Point Four and Liberia, and What It Is-Point Four-How it Works, 1951-1971. 1953, 1951-1953 (Folder 5-7)
        - Citizens Foreign Aid Committee. Form letters, newsletters, printed reports, 1959-1971 (Folder 8-9)
      - International banking. Newsletters and pamphlet, SEE ALSO: United States-Foreign relations/United Nations/Economic assistance, 1951-1983. (Folder 10)
      - Trade
        - General. Charts, pamphlets, report, 1953-1975. (Folder 11)
        - Communist countries. Charts, clippings, correspondence, flyers, form letters, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, releases, reports, transcripts, c. 1952-1975
          - General, c. 1952-1975
            - Non-printed material, Includes mimeographed copy of Robert M. Bleiberg, Less Trade with the Bear, and mimeographed statements by William E. Jenner, Karl Mundt and George Bender, and Harold Stassen, c. 1952- c. 1968. (Folder 12)
            - Printed material, 1953-1974 (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
          - Grain (Folder 3)
            - General. Includes mimeographed facts sheets issued by the U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, and statements by Thomas J. Dodd, Paul Findley, and George McGovern, 1963-1975
            - Correspondence with the American Farm Bureau Federation, William Loeb, and others, 1966
    - Foreign Policy Association (Folder 4-5)
      - General. Flyers, newsletters, pamphlets, resolutions, serial issues. Includes a series of printed reports, Decision... 1957, 1957-1962
      - Correspondence with C. Ralph Nichols, 1960-1961
    - Immigration
      - General. Clippings, newsletters, pamphlets, c. 1953-1971 (Folder 6)
      - Refugees. Clipping, flyer, pamphlets, 1959-1974 (Folder 7)
    - Information agencies
      - General. Memoranda, newsletters, pamphlet, press releases, reports, typescript radio broadcast transcript, a mimeographed transcript of Eugene W. Castle, How to Win the Cold War, and a printed copy of U.S. Information Service, 11th Report to Congress, 1950-1961 (Folder 8-9)
      - Correspondence with Everett Dirksen, the U.S. Information Agency, and others, 1958-1971 (Folder 10)
    - Peace Corps. Newsletters, 1961 (Folder 11)
    - Senate Foreign Relations Committee. Newsletter, notes, printed hearing transcripts, 1960-1966 (Folder 12)
    - State Department
      - General. Newsletters, notes, pamphlets, press releases, reports, reprints, serial issues, and a mimeographed transcript of Jerome M. Frank, Psychological Aspects of Foreign Affairs, Newsletters, notes, pamphlets, press releases, reports, reprints, serial issues, and a mimeographed transcript of Jerome M. Frank, Psychological Aspects of Foreign Affairs, 1950-1977 1950-1977 (Folder 13-14)
      - Correspondence with Russell Kirk and Jay Sourwine, 1963-1964 (Box 36)
    - Treaties and alliances. SEE ALSO: United States-Foreign relations/United Nations/Treaties
      - General. Printed transcript of speech by John W. Bricker, newsletter, 1952-1953 (Folder 1)
      - Central Treaty Organization (CENTO). Delegation lists for 1959 conference, flyer, maps
      - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO)
        - General. Charts, correspondence, pamphlets, newsletters, printed reports, transcripts, printed copy of Matthew B. Ridgway, Second Annual Report of the Supreme Commander of Allied Forces in Europe (in French), and mimeographed transcript of Thomas C. Darcy, NATO Objectives and Organization, 1953-1975 (Folder 2-3)
        - U.S. Army, Europe. Biographical sketches, poster, reports, serial issues (USAREUR Information Bulletin), and mimeographed report, United States Army, Europe, Today, 1960-1961 (Folder 4)
    - United Nations
      - General, 1948-1974
        - General. Correspondence, declaration, flyers, memoranda, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, press releases, transcripts, statements by Ernest A. Gross and James J. Wadsworth, 1948-1974 (Folder 5)
        - Anti-United Nations. Newsletters, notes, pamphlets, printed copies of Ten Years of the United Nations...Soviet's Greatest Hoax, and Myron C. Fagan, Documentation of U.N. Plot to Destroy U.S., 1950-1962 (Folder 6)
      - Armed Forces. Memoranda, newsletters, notes, pamphlets, 1951-1957 (Folder 7)
      - Commission on Human Rights (Folder 8)
        - General. Flyers, newsletters, pamphlets, 1948-1978
        - Correspondence with the State Department, 1951
      - Economic assistance programs. Charts, newsletters, pamphlets, 1952-1975 (Folder 9)
      - Finance. Newsletter and printed budget reports, 1952-1964 (Folder 10-11)
      - Flag. Pamphlet, 1950 (Folder 12)
      - Headquarters. Printed pamphlets and hearing transcript, c. 1967
      - Information services. Lists of films, newsletter, program schedules, 1951-1955 (Folder 13)
        - General. Charts, pamphlet, 1952-1955 (Folder 14)
        - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO). Pamphlet (Folder 15)
        - International Civil Aviation Organization (ICAO). Pamphlet, 1950 (Folder 16)
        - International Labor Organization (ILO). Newsletter, notes, pamphlets, press release, 1955-1958 (Box 37, Folder 1)
        - International Trade Organization (ITO). Pamphlet, 1949 (Folder 2)
        - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO)
          - General, 1949-1962
            - General. Flyers, list of publications, newsletters, reprints, tables, speech transcript, mimeographed report on UNESCO, printed copy of Florence Fowler Lyons, Reports on UNESCO (pamphlet and newsletters), 1949-1962 (Folder 3-4)
            - Correspondence with Karl E. Mundt, 1955 (Folder 5)
          - Budget. Mimeographed memoranda and reports, FY 1954 (Folder 6)
          - Education. Correspondence, list of publications, newsletters, pamphlets, reports, transcripts, 1949-1962 (Folder 7-9)
        - United Nations International Children's Emergency Fund (UNICEF). Pamphlet, 1952 (Folder 10)
        - World Health Organization (WHO). Pamphlet, 1951 (Folder 11)
        - World Meteorological Organization (WMO). Pamphlet, 1951 (Folder 12)
      - International trusteeships. Chart and pamphlets, 1951-1952 (Folder 13)
      - Officials and employees (Folder 14)
        - General. Biographical sketches, newsletters, press releases, mimeographed statements by William E. Jenner, Henry Cabot Lodge, Jr., and John T. Wood, 1952-1977
        - Correspondence with Henry Cabot Lodge, Jr., 1953-1958
      - Organizational structure
        - General
          - General. Chart and mimeographed reports, Structure of the United Nations (5th and 6th revisions), 1952-1953 (Folder 15)
          - Charter. Newsletter, pamphlets, report, 1945-1955 (Folder 16)
        - General Assembly (Folder 17)
          - General. Chart and pamphlet, 1952
          - Secretariat. Chart and reports, The Secretariat of the United Nations (mimeograph) and Organization of the Secretariat (printed), 1951-1952
        - International Court of Justice. Article, clipping, flyer, newsletter, reprint, transcript, 1959-1960 (Folder 18)
        - Security Council. Chart and newsletter, 1952-1964 (Folder 19)
      - Treaties. Clipping, flyer, newsletter, 1953-1977 (Folder 20)
      - World government. Clippings, flyers, memoranda, newsletters, pamphlets, serial issue (The Freeman) reports, mimeographed statements by Rose L. Martin, Francis J. McNamara, and Gardner Osborn, 1951-1972 (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
    - World War II, 1939-1945
      - General. Newsletters, photocopies of newspapers, press releases, and uncorrected galleys of State Department report on Malta and Yalta conferences, Parts I and II, 1938-1976 (Folder 3)
      - Pearl Harbor. Newsletters and report, 1942-1961 (Folder 4)
      - War crimes and international justice. Chart, clipping, legal briefs, 1950-1962 (Folder 5)
  - United States - Government
    - General. Biographical sketches, clippings, flyers, form letter, newsletters, notes, and correspondence with John E. Moss and others, c. 1959-c. 1978 (Folder 6)
    - Constitution. Correspondence, clipping, flyer, pamphlet, press release, reports, 1960-1961 (Folder 7)
    - Executive branch. Biographical sketches, chart, newsletters, printed report, 1957-1977 (Folder 8)
    - Intelligence agencies
      - General. Newsletters and notes, 1975 (Folder 9)
      - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA) (Folder 10)
        - General, Newsletters. Includes printed report, H.R. bill and a typescript memorandum with notes, relating to the establishment of the CIA, c. 1944-1975. c. 1944
        - Correspondence with Allen W. Dulles, Alfred Kohlberg and others, 1955-1959
        - General
          - General. Biographical sketch, bulletin, flyer, newsletters, notes, press releases, printed hearing transcript, serial issue (FBI Law Enforcement Bulletin), 1961-1976 (Folder 11)
          - Annual reports. Printed copies, 1963 and 1965 (Box 39, Folder 1)
        - Hoover, J. Edgar. Clippings, reprint, statement before the House Un-American Activities Committee, 1947-1965 (Folder 2)
    - Judicial branch
      - General. Correspondence, flyer, newsletter, photocopy of material relating to grand jury procedures, 1972-1973 (Folder 3)
      - Supreme Court (Folder 4-5)
        - General. Biographical sketches, newsletters, pamphlets, reprints, printed and mimeographed transcripts of speeches by William E. Jenner, typescript copy of speech by James O. Eastland, 1954-1970
        - Correspondence with Jay Sourwine, 1955
    - Legislative branch
      - General. Clipping, flyer, newsletters, 1953-1970 (Folder 6)
      - Congress. Form letter, legal brief, newsletters, notes, resolution, 1955-1967 (Folder 7)
  - United States - Politics
    - General
      - General (Folder 8)
        - General. Flyer, pamphlets, mimeographed reports of the Senate Minority Policy Committee, What the Country Got Out of 19 Democratic Years and 12 Republican Years, and of Public Affairs Counsellor, Inc., The A-B-C's of Applied Citizenship Training, 1951-1959
        - Correspondence from Eugene W. Castle to Anne Wheaton, and Everett Dirksen, 1958
      - Americanism (patriotism) (Folder 9)